- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_MB_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_02_InnTutorial_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_MB_Grace_01A
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_03_VaultTutorial_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT2
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_04_MeetPayne_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 9.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_AllyaMusa
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 9.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_EliasDerit
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT2
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_07_FreeMiners_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 10.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_EliasDerit
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_07
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_08_DestroyRune_Obj_Response_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 10.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_09_ReturnRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 10.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_alt
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 10.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Success_alt
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 10.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_SerPayneBennett_03
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_10
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT2
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Proposal_Prompt_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@NPC_DefaultDialogue_05_RegentJinJae"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 11.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_SerPayneBennett_03
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_13
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_12
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT2_Footwear_15
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_13_StormBeach_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 12.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_SerPayneBennett_03
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_15
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_13
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT2_Legwear_15
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_Obj_Response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 12.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_16
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_16_FastTravel_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 13.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_MB_Moira_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_17
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_16
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: amuletmonarchsblufft3
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 14.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_MB_Moira_03
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_18
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_17
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT2_Handwear_15
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_18_InspectStatue_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 14.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_PercillaWallen
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_19
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_18
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT2
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_NPCGreet_Moira_07"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 15.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_PercillaWallen
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_20
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_19
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT2_Chestwear_15
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_20_CollectCrown_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 15.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_MB_Grace_03
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_21
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_20
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 16.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_PercillaWallen_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_22
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_21
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: HoningStoneT2
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_22_DestroyShrine_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_23_ToTower
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 16.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_PercillaWallen_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_23
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_22
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT2
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_23_ToTower_Obj_Response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 16.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_PercillaWallen_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_23
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_24_DefeatGawain_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_destroyer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Warmonger
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_destroyer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_musketeer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Musketeer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_musketeer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_mystic
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Theurgist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_mystic
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_occultist
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Occultist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_occultist
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_ranger
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Tracker
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_ranger
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_soldier
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Mercenary
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_soldier
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_swordsman
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_RegentJinJae_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_24 && Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Success_swordsman
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_MSQ_25_CrownRegent_Obj_Response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_00
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: MSQ_00_init
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Headgear_20
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_alt
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_00
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: MSQ_00_init
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_25
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Success_alt
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Headgear_20
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Start_Prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Proposal_a_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_MSQ_26_ToYonas_Obj_Incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@06A_MSQ_22_TalkToSoulwarden_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_FionaMurphy
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_01_PlaceFlowers_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_02_GatherGift
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_EddaYonkers
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_02
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_02_GatherGift_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_03_CollectPicks
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_CemalQadir
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_03_CollectPicks_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 9.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_AsheDubois_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_13
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_04_ExplodeBarrels_Obj_Response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 11.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_HugoMolina
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_16
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_05_ArtifactShards_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_07_ForgeRing
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 12.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_JeongNabi
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_19
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_07_ForgeRing_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_08_GatherFangs
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 12.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_HamzaKillic
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_19
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_08_GatherFangs_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_09_CollectGlass
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 14.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_OliviaBarovier
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_19
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_09_CollectGlass_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_10_BreakCurse
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 14.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_HugoMolina_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_Side_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_10_BreakCurse_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 15.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_DayoMusa
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_11
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_21
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_11_ClericAmulets_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_AsheDubois
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_21 && 12A_Side_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_12_KnightsCrest_Obj_Response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_13_DevilHoney
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_GeertieLother
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_13
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_13_DevilHoney_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_14_CollectWine
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 9.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_GeertieLother
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_14
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_Side_13
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "1"
  Title: "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_14_CollectWine_Obj_Response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_15_CollectResources
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_CemalQadir
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_15
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_Side_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "FALSE"
  Title: "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_15_CollectResources_Obj_Response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 12_CemalQadir
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_16
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_Side_15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: 12A_Side_17_MarketBoard
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "FALSE"
  Title: "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Start_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@12A_Side_16_ToGoodUse_Obj_Response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 12A_Side_17_MarketBoard
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 7.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12A_Side_17
  RequiredAchievementId: 12A_Side_16
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "FALSE"
  Title: "@12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Obj_Title"
  Description: "@12A_Side_17_MarketBoard_Obj_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: ""
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: ""
  InProgressResponse: ""
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: ""
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "1"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: null
  RewardType: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0101_downpayment_MB
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 14.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0101a_d_00_container_downpayment
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoChason
  ExclusiveTerritory: 12.0
  AchievementId: S_downpayment
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: QuestRewardHousing1
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0101_downpayment_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0101_downpayment_FL
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 14.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0101d_d_00_container_downpayment
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoChason
  ExclusiveTerritory: 6.0
  AchievementId: S_downpayment
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: QuestRewardHousing1
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0101_downpayment_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0101_downpayment_EF
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 14.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0101c_d_00_container_downpayment
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoChason
  ExclusiveTerritory: 4.0
  AchievementId: S_downpayment
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: QuestRewardHousing1
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0101_downpayment_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0101_downpayment_WW
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 14.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0101d_d_00_container_downpayment
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoChason
  ExclusiveTerritory: 6.0
  AchievementId: S_downpayment
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: QuestRewardHousing1
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0101_downpayment_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0101_downpayment_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0101_downpayment_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0201_majorpurchase
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 18.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0201_d_00_container_majorpurchase
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoChason
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_2
  RequiredAchievementId: S_downpayment
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: House_HousingItem_Chair_Settler_Chair01_A
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0201_majorpurchase_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 21.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0301_d_00_container_insuringinvestmentA
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoTravelersA
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_3a
  RequiredAchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_2
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0301_insuringinvestmentA_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 23.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0302_d_00_container_insuringinvestmentB
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoTravelersA
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_3b
  RequiredAchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_3a
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: House_HousingItem_Storage_T1_ChestOldLog
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0302_insuringinvestmentB_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0401_siteinspection
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 30.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0401_d_00_container_siteinspection
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoTravelersA
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_4
  RequiredAchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_3b
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: House_HousingItem_Bed_Settler_Bed02_A
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0401_siteinspection_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0401_siteinspection_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0401_siteinspection_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0401_siteinspection_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0401_siteinspection_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0401_siteinspection_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 37.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0501_d_00_container_mandatoryimprovements
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoTravelersB
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_5
  RequiredAchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_4
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0501_mandatoryimprovements_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 1225_0601_closingcost
  Type: SkillProgression
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 50.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 1225_0601_d_00_container_closingcost
  NpcDestinationId: 1225_GiacomoTravelersB
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_6
  RequiredAchievementId: 12_Quest_Housing_5
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: QuestRewardHousing7
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: "0"
  Title: "@1225_0601_closingcost_objective_title"
  Description: "@1225_0601_closingcost_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_0601_closingcost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@1225_0601_closingcost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@1225_0601_closingcost_incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@1225_0601_closingcost_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  RewardWithPlayerLevel: true
  RewardType: Quest+
  NOTE: ""
